▍2026 辛辛那提 ATP1000 第二轮
法里亚 6-4 6-4 谢尔顿 · 赛后场上采访
Jaime, huge congratulations.
海梅 恭喜你
We saw you sitting on the chair at the end
我们看到你坐在椅子上
of the match.
坐了很久
What were you thinking about?
那会儿你在想什么
Who were you thinking about?
你想到的是谁
What did it mean to you?
这场胜利对你意味着什么
I was thinking about those guys on the box.
我想的是包厢里那几个人
Just very emotional moment for me
对我来说是很动感情的一刻
and for my team.
对我的团队也是
It's like we made it moment.
那种感觉是 我们做到了
And yeah, just to do it here
而且就是在这儿
in front of an amazing crowd
台下这么棒的观众
against the home player at night.
对手还是主场球员 又是夜场
This amazing venue just makes it
这么好的球场
a little more special.
让这一切更特别了
And yeah,
是啊
I'm just enjoying my first top ten win.
这是我第一次赢下世界前十
So those moments,
这样的时刻
you've got to take it all in and just enjoy.
你得把它全部收下 好好享受
You've been on the rise.
你这阵子一直在往上走
Were you expecting something like
这样的一场胜利
this to happen?
你预料到了吗
I don't know.
我说不好
I worked for these moments.
我一直在为这样的时刻努力
I'm going to be honest.
说实话
I don't know. I started the year not so well.
我也说不好 今年开局并不好
Trying to just get in the top 100.
当时只想着先进世界前一百
I don't know.
真说不好
What's changed?
那是什么变了
Beat my mentality.
我的心态吧
Work ethic maybe.
还有训练的态度
Just trying to focus more on the process.
更专注在过程上
Not too much when these moments
不去想这些时刻
are going to happen.
什么时候会到
It will happen.
它会到的
It happens.
它就是会到
That's why I'm so happy
所以我才这么高兴
because I'm focusing on the process,
因为我专注的是过程
not taking steps ahead of time.
没有想着一步登天
And yeah, in these moments you've got
而这样的时刻
to celebrate.
就该好好庆祝
Because mentally you were tested
今天你的心理被反复考验
so many times today.
考验了很多次
You came back at you hard at the end
第一盘末段他追得很凶
of the first set and you were a breakdown
第二盘你还被破发
in the second.
落后了
You thought clearly
那些时刻你的头脑
in those moments today.
一直很清楚
Yeah, sure. I was 4 -1 down on this set.
确实 这一盘我一比四落后
I made five games in a row
然后连赢五局
against Ben Shelton in this center court.
对手是谢尔顿 还是在中央球场
Not easy, so I'm just really focused
不容易 所以我就是很专注
and with really a routine.
老老实实按流程来
Well, wish you luck for the next round.
祝你下一轮好运
Well done.
打得漂亮
Thank you.
谢谢